hello nice to meet you
nice to meet you I'm Riley hi
I'm the manager Pangmin Young
welcome to Danjang I'm Riley nice to meet you also
you're so beautiful
and you're humble yeah
oh didn't know yeah
I I studied abroad in South Korea a couple years ago
so I was able to rent it and go to the palace
so did you speak Korean a little
just a little bit I only yeah
I can only understand a little bit
but it's been a while so I don't
that's perfect
that's okay we'll do our best
my name is Riley I'm 24 years old
I live in New York City and I work as a personal color consultant
um in 2,021
I actually studied abroad in South Korea
and of course I was shopping at olive
looking for makeup and Learned about personal color through
through that and so
I decided to look up and do a deep dive
in the personal color analysis
the way I do I've been working as a personal color consultant
for a little over two years now
you know isn't it like a very common in LA to
it wasn't when I first started um
when I first started about two years ago
it was maybe us and another studio
but now there's some more studios popping up
especially in Korea Town oh okay
especially in Korea Town yeah okay
um do you have a
like a certain image of like a makeover
um I'm thinking something
usually what I do for my makeup is a little bit more youthful
and kind of cutie natural yeah
so I'm thinking I want something a little bit more mature and romantic
okay like a little bit more elegant elegant yeah
baby yeah
outfit that I'm thinking of wearing
it's a soft purple kind of tighter dress
and it has a little bit of a cowl neck
and I brought white heels to wear with it okay
so it's very feminine right very feminine
and what's your plan for today
so my plans for today
I my husband and I are just gonna go out on a date oh
that's romantic yeah
yeah yeah
you're gonna be more beautiful yeah I'm excited
oh hey
hi you made it haha
oh haha
your stand wife is very beautiful very pretty I I like her a lot oh
yes I can yeah yeah
네
so maybe sit here have a seat here
perfect yeah
아 아 옆에 놀까
어
어떻게 된 거예요 아
여기 퍼스널 컬러 엔젤리스트 시도해요 아 그래서 언니 오신 거예요 한번
받아보려고 아이 손님이신데 장가 아우 오케이
what colors do you normally like to wear
Aubrey Cora Aubrey
yeah
so we'll start with looking at your jewelry first
looking at your jewelry first
here is gold jewelry gold jewelry it's a little too yellow right
yeah so this here is a bit too yellow
but here you see how bright your skin looks your skin really pops
your under eyes look great
your eyes light up it looks great
I got gold do you like it
I think it's nice gold look a little bit older to be with you
so these are warm colors when we look at warm colors on you
along with when we look at the red here
if we compare this red it's warm versus cool
the cool brings out a really nice color in your lips
your eyes look great are you supposed to move a little
hair looks nice and rich
and so instead of being warm where your skin goes a little green
어 이렇게 보니까 좀 차이가 있네
and we do the same thing with the blues
so we've got a bright warm blue you see how it's reflecting
right there very blue
and then if you look here
yeah nice lifted oh yes yeah it's really good it's pretty
good
and I've got match pastel color oh
yeah not as many pastels I think I've got
oh the pink is running to go oh you're going to make an
so bright pink
versus fuchsia and again really nice jawline eyes are popping
so you are definitely winter
winter you're a cool winter yeah cool winter
I thought it was summer
I was a cold woman, winter. I thought I was a very warm person, but winter.
Karl Lagerfeld so this is more
Really gorgeous and you can wear
shinier fabrics so silks and satins work really well and
jewel tones work very well on you yeah bright things look good on me
Oh, I look good in bright colors. I'm cleaning up.
I have to do it, go home, ah haha ah
thank you so much of course I'm glad that you enjoyed it
and this is your time to make over so yeah now it's my turn
shall we go for makeup thank you
hi I'm a makeup artist for you today I'm Riley nice to meet you
let's see her
okay
you have dry skin I think so it's kind of combination
I don't have anything on it right now and it's pretty dry okay
it's a sun sunscreen
okay
I heard you were in Korea for study
yeah yeah I studied abroad there yeah for what study
um I was studying culture and art culture and art yeah
I really like the
when you walk through Seoul a lot of the storefronts
look really pretty and they're put together and they have themes
and so I liked walking around and yeah
and in New York you see scaffolding on the front of every building
우리 일터
and so I liked not seeing all the scaffolding and actually
seeing the pretty buildings
but then in Seoul when I was walking
around a lot of the a lot of the buildings have really pretty
storefronts do you miss Korea
I do I really liked living there oh
so fun
what are you gonna do after this makeup
probably go out to dinner dinner yeah there's a steakhouse in
steakhouse yeah
there's a steakhouse in Brooklyn
so we have to go get my my husband changed and then we'll go oh really
look please thank you
oh hey
oh hey I'm Daniel
nice to meet you hey
how's it going how's it going
oh
you wanna have a seat first
oh yeah
yeah thank you
hi Lilly's husband
yes yes
what's your name Isaac Isaac Yep
Isaac yep
nice to meet you nice to meet you try the Yakult yep okay
thank you
누구의 마이크 쓰시는데 아 라일리 라일리의 남편인가 아
you wanna say hello to your wife yeah yeah let's go
ha ha you got a good yeah mustache yeah say hello
hey
say hello
hi hey you made it haha I ain't gonna see you oh
haha
you made you got lost
you made you got lost yeah
I was running so fast to make it here oh my gosh yeah cool
are you gonna wait but he just say hello before before makeup
I'll see you later bye
let's go alright
okay
the time your boyfriend mm hmm wow
yeah he's so sweet yeah
yeah he's my husband we got
we've been married for almost three years now
really yeah yeah how long does do you guys dated dated
for two years before we got married
so we've been together for almost five years now oh yeah yeah sounds
good yeah we actually met before I studied abroad
so part of our relationship
I was in Korea for huh
while he was here and we did long distance
I was in Korea for long distance
yeah
oh my God yeah
40 about uh yeah
yeah hours lonely right
yeah yeah
wow that's a real love
yeah and then we went back to Korea together and I showed him like
all the places where I was like
this is where I went I would Facetime you
this is what I was showing you when I was on the phone
you know wow
yeah
I will so I
what do you do uh
I mount TVs I'm on
you're on TV uh
or I I put them up on the wall ah
okay okay
ah okay
yeah what do you call sort of more like a handyman
a handyman yeah
ah sounds cool
we mount or I mount TVs
art shelves here look actually
oh let me show you
we got do you work every day
pretty much yeah
yeah I try to take some days off
cause I carry this backpack with me and it's pretty heavy
what yeah
haha what what
yeah seriously
what's in it it's all in my pocket
oh my God yeah
that's why you got muscles
oh thank you
like Dush dush dush haha
dush dush dush haha dush dush dush
I want to know your love story oh
how did you meet how did you meet
um so we met in college
it was a really small school so we knew each other but not really okay
and then um I graduated I'm a couple years older than her okay
and one day it was during the summer of 2020
I had a dream and she was in the dream whoa
and I woke up and I went that's weird
so you're in the closet yeah
no I had I had so I was here in New York
she was in California so I thought she wasn't here
so I pick up my phone
and she posts on Instagram that she's in New York whoa
so I just dropped her a message and said hey uh
do you wanna go out yes
she said yes what
and that's kind of how we met what
what
it it's it's crazy that's crazy
when did you guys get married
three years ago three years ago yeah
yeah 3 October 15th
wow yeah
oh amazing
what is your undertone
I'm summer summer
summer mute summer mute yeah
so pretty I love this yeah color
thank you summer Mute this person uses color
He also runs a shop here and now.
He is a person who knows himself well.
Well, I was a bit like this, wondering what I should save.
I'm gonna use only natural makeup I think
and then freckles so
can I see your outfit the pictures yes yes
ah it's like a little bit mauve pink yes
ah it's okay to see dress
color that is the first thing that is important to me
dress color that is just make up
a very important good thing they do it all over
purple pink
But no matter who sees that
It's an eye shadow color. Ah, I have to keep Jeong-eun as is. I don't like it.
I brought this for this today’s look
I'm gonna match this color with your outfit perfect
the first I'm gonna use this color to mix yeah yeah okay
so pretty
no gonna be on my team
and then second color is dress color
use the color the middle of the egg is set like this
oh yeah that looks nice that's not bad right no
I tried to draw it before but I never knew where to put it
because I don't really have much there oh oh really yeah
they're totally changing
so pretty and then let's try first lashes hmm
this is also the first time I've worn lashes before ah really
they feel weird hahaha
looks so pretty thank you
yeah it's gonna be the the feeling is awkward yeah because some shadow
under my eyes yeah yeah yeah I know that feeling cool
so pretty oh my God we can use this the lower line
it's gonna be so so perfect match with your dress colour
oh that looks pretty pretty yeah
it's good and then does some glitter
you can use upper the small teeth
this area
so pretty and then the bigger one the middle of the egg is there
oh I like that it's really pretty
OK
yeah I love that that's so pretty so pretty
this looks like a goddess
oh thank you
yeah really yeah
oh
that'll do it
아 아 진짜 예쁘다
예쁘죠 음 너무 예쁘다 아니 그
드레스 컬러가 나한테 엄청 큰 인스파이어를 줬어 그걸 그렇죠 컬러 딱
보자마자 나도 드레스 보고
나도 드레스 보고 머리가 딱 해야겠다 나
I've heard your love story how you guys met yeah
Isaac is so lovely haha
lovely yeah lovely man he's like a puppy yeah
like a poodle
like a poodle hahaha with the curly hair yeah yeah so cute
Okay, will you walk?
Don Bracelet haha but it feels so different I made it but it looks good on me
I think
So pretty
Oh, it's so pretty. What grade is it? Um.
wow hmm it's pretty
you are green I think green or blue green and blue yeah wow
it's like a doll it's like a doll
your eye color it's so unique
It's really pretty. Yes, the texture is really pretty too.
That's right, that pattern is called turtle sherry, and those turtle sherry eyes
The patterns are all a bit different.
may I see it yeah
Wow, that thing on the meat shell is similar to the hexagon.
I guess so, oh rare wow
I am Korean chef Korean chef Korean chef
yeah my hometown is a Paju Paju
Paju Brown yeah the name is Paju Brown Paju my hometown oh
you heard it yourself Korea
I think you have the prettiest beauty chair. If you give me any doubts, well.
Now, how do I express it’s mysterious?
is mysterious sounds like weird
mysterious no not really but that's sounds right that sounds right
yeah oh OK a lot of people like mysterious
Wow, it’s amazing
so nice
do you like this TT yes I love that oh
예술 예술을 하시는
거 같아요 진짜 아이고 그거는 거기다이 메이크업 해야 되겠죠 멋있다
오징어 오징어
have a seat ha ha
it's in 진짜 진짜 really really almost done
OK ha ha ha a few a few minutes a few minutes
haha are you nervous
a little bit a little bit I think I can do this ha ha ha ha ha
OK ha ha ha you alright
출발했습니다
she's coming
open open open my name is Riley I'm 24 years old
I live in New York City and I work as a personal color consultant
2,021 I actually studied abroad in South Korea
of course I was shopping at olive and looking for makeup
and Learned about personal color through through that and so I
decided to look up and do a deep dive into personal color analysis
my husband and I are just gonna go out on a date
haha yeah that's so romantic yeah
nice to meet you I'm Riley hi I'm the manager Park Min Young
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait open
open open tada
wah open open wah oh my God
oh
I cannot focus on anything but you baby I cannot focus on anything
but you chop chop the hate them but you're
my beautiful baby I cannot focus on anything on anyone
so pretty oh
so cute
The makeup stands yay thank you so pretty
Thank You Your Welcome is so crazy
I was really surprised by the makeup. The after-effects were the prettiest I've ever seen.
No, because of the dress line, I said I should get rid of it earlier, but the dress has this cold line.
of drapline
It's a dress that's on point. The details of your outfit are really important.
I thought I couldn't cover it up by pulling it down with my hair.
This hairstyle is princess
ship style Oh, my husband will really like it.
It's Kibidi's nose. It's so pretty. It's so pretty.
yeah I really like the whole style cause it still feels like me
a slightly more elevated version so
and since I'm coming from the color analysis perspective I appreciate
when all of the colors in my makeup match well together the eyeshadow
the blush
the lip everything matches really well together you're all I'm seeing
oh my god
how are you doing oh my goodness
you look fantastic
oh my god oh my god
yeah
oh
It's really pretty
thank you
haha thank you haha oh my gosh you like it yeah I do I like how um
her hair goes behind her ears too yeah oh my goodness
yeah I always wear my hair down so he never sees my whole face yeah
you like the hair mm hmm mm hmm
it looks pretty right behind the ear yeah yeah
hahaha
thank you
you alright
you're so shy you're so shy
Ah, it's pretty, you did a great job. Ah, you like it so much. Really kiss her kiss her
there you go so you don't mess up the makeup
yeah keep
keep my lipstick yeah
I I don't yeah
yeah yeah
haha
oh yeah
and then we'll go to dinner
haha
I know I need to take you out on a date now
oh my goodness yeah hahaha
Real honey away, real honey away, honey away, honey away, honey away
thank you it was nice meeting you thank you thank you for coming
good evening have a good day bye bye
have a good time bye bye enjoy your time
Goodbye haha
Pronunciation What is the pronunciation? Haha. Everyone, let’s get together quickly. Decoration, decoration, flower decoration
I finished putting out my clothes. Thank you for your hard work today. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
grab your worries come sit down come sit down
outside OK yeah we all
I'll choose the real over the fake any day
I'll choose the real over the fake
Hello, hi, hi, I'm pretty. How many minutes are left? There's a lot left now.
There's one left. It's five minutes before ten. Five minutes before ten. Five minutes before ten. Let's meet up.
check it out check it out
That day
It's coming, it's one o'clock. Time really flies, right?
I can't believe that today is the last day of business haha. That's right.
It's strange, it's strange
I think I'll keep doing it. I need to put a lot of space here so I can take pictures with my eyes.
Take a picture
Ah, I guess I'll be sad. Ah, I'm sad right now, honestly, ah, what should I do if that's already happened? Fighting.
Fighting, fighting, fighting, we too, fighting, fighting
Fighting, I'm burning fire today
Now, I'm burning really hot today, really.
Today is the last day, OK A, leader, leader, soon leader
Haha, no, today is the last day of vocalization ah.
But suddenly, as if it was the day before, I suddenly came to my senses.
It was so fast, you act like it was the day before.
disability disability flower dan disability
Are you coming now?
But it won't open and I'm shaking so scary here.
It's almost like greeting the chairman. Oh, that's right, yes.
Haha, I'm nervous haha. It feels like the first day. Oh, it feels like the first day. Oh, it looks like you're coming up, really.
Almost all of them will feature super battles, but the angle is different, so who will go first?
uh slightly
It feels like a battle. It’s really six, six against six, six against six, six against six.
hello
hello nice to meet you hello hello victoria yes
hi hi
I'm Mira
nice to meet you nice to meet you hello Daniel
nice to meet you Victoria hi I'm the manager of Hollywood
I'm such a fan of you oh thank you Mary my husband was like my
favorite oh thank you so much Victoria's
mom oh yes nice to meet you it's a pleasure what's your name
it's Mary Vic yes Mary Vic yes
yes nice to meet you what's your name Yondela Yondela
Yondela oh I'm Tiffany Tiffany Tiffany Sarah Sarah
come this way please yeah here
아
저기 일하다 오셨나 봐요 어 어 네
옷을 입고 계시네요 어 no I I saw that your face was
a part of it but I didn't know I'd meet you personally oh yes
so um we have a welcome menu welcome menu
drink yes and for you thank you we have some drinks
oh my goodness and next page we have some snacks too oh so
it's very Korean but no
I love it yes
I love it I like this
this looks really good yeah
keep
a bottle of water is really good for your puffiness in the morning
oh good I need that OK
I need that thank you so much and what about you guys
yes can I get the lemon
can I get the lemon can I get the lemon
oh my gosh that's why I was just gonna say I'm so sorry cause I
I watch K pop drama cause I said that's why I said
oh my gosh I
I love that I was just like
she looks like her but me I said I don't want oh my gosh
um marry my marry my husband
yes I
I love that one yes
your dad's gonna be blown away
are you serious
to have a seat here thank you
so how are you feeling about whole makeover today
I'm so excited you're excited
I am yes
is this your first time to get a full makeover
it is yeah
um I don't really have too much time to take care of myself
so I can see your office
you are definitely a doctor maybe
I am yeah
oh really I'm a second year resident uh
in neurology oh really
yeah that's amazing
thank you so what made you to you
know become a doctor or um
my um
my mom outside actually she has um
a neurological condition that we don't fully understand yet
so I grew up uh
seeing her in a lot of pain
yes um
and having symptoms like not able to control her muscles sometimes
so I was really interested in the brain
I studied it in college and then I became a brain doctor
because I want to help people like her
the doctors that took care of her are doctors that inspired me
and she's a nurse so I grew up in the hospital next to her
you have a sweetheart thank you
I it's
I'm so glad she's here with me
I just I
she's my best friend
me and my mom are also my besties
so I totally understand your situation
and yeah do you have a
like a allergies or consultation over your skin
that's what's hard at night
sometimes I come home I work 16 hours and
or 14 16 hours and then I just fall asleep
I'm happy if I brush my teeth
so hard to you know
being a doctor
but it's worth it I'm glad
yeah it's glad yeah
my name is Victoria Castillo
I am 28 years old and I'm a second year neurology resident
in medicine it's really easy to focus so much on other people
and forget to take time for yourself for rest and self care
that's why I wanted to come to
things like this so that I can fill my own cup again
and feel more in touch with who I am
so that I can give back to others and more
hi I'm Victoria so we are ready
so let's get started about your makeup
thank you so much
do you want to the wash your shampoo today
yeah that's only that's fine
yes ah okay
I'm gonna rinse you like like this yeah
okay yeah okay just have a sit
oh yours curly hair is very nice it's shape then little bit dry
uh huh yes
today is I apply this and very hydration and nourishing OK
thank you OK
that sounds amazing I I never know how to hydrate it
oh yeah I feel like it gets dry so fast
don't worry it's normal can I take off your glasses
yes yes
OK I keep your eye
thank you I'll recline your chair OK
can you come up a little bit please thank you
marry my husband she's the one
she's the one
she's the main she's the main character there
I know that's why it's like that's why it can be
오늘 어머님이 어머님이 빅팬이셔가지고 아
아 저
그걸 많이 보셔가지고
oh you look so young hahaha thanks dear hahaha
we're all the same age yeah
I'm kind of like trying to blend in there hahaha
you can be sit together
oh yeah thank you that's why you're my favorite
actress of all my drama
I did watch your thing
that's why when we walked in
I said my husband's not gonna believe I love how you did that show oh
can I give you a hug oh my gosh I I can I give you a hug
I tell you I got a I got a blouse like what you were wearing
I said it looks so good on you I said I probably would look good
I almost wore it today
엄마는 여전히 이쁘네요
I said oh my God you you were so good in that show
oh my gosh thank you so much oh my gosh take a picture oh yes yes
oh my gosh family together yeah it's really cute
family together yeah it's really cute
oh my God thank you so much
oh my gosh my family in the Philippines wouldn't believe it
oh oh my gosh I'm gonna send it to my husband
look around really look around okay okay
okay let's go look around let's go yeah
which one is autumn
oh wow this is an interesting texture
if you have all the one will feel less pressure
that's one yeah OK cool
look in the mirror to see if you want more blush
oh that is good gently that's good okay good
thank you you're welcome
so nice to have so many daughters
to take care of me with all this challenging things the perks
the perks
it's so good thank you I really like this one
you look like a model all together
I look at you on the pictures
like that's my Hispanic little model right there
how was your shampoo today
oh my gosh I could have fallen asleep
was it good it was really great
thank you so much thank you thank you
you are a saint
your job cruise yes
oh really
yes I'm a doctor
wow
very smart that's amazing
thank you thank you so much
so smart so you just worked here now
um I
I was working here before
should we go yes
thank you today your big change is not doctor today is an influencer
yeah yeah
that was a big change OK leave it to me
so are you going back to work
ah not after this
not after this yes yeah
you're very good job many people's get can't do your job
thank you so important
which part is it uh
I'm in neurology so the neurology brain brain oh
haha wow
you have check on my brain too
is there any easy test easy test
usually we just ask people in the hospital
do you know who you are do you know when you are
so I'm Daniel mm hmm
I mean right now
what is right now what month is it
it's August it's August
he's great do you know where you are
I'm in Korea you're in Korea
oh no
no no no get him from the scanner
it's your job it's not your
job yeah
right not enough for us to leave yeah
I met the in Korea it's many resident to doctor aha
it's very messed up here hahaha
inan in a pushy and ah it's same me lolly yeah
I see yeah
it's a 2 party and lolly
I keep wanting to learn how to be better
but I just it's so hard to find time
ha ha fast
very easy to manage it very easy
yes
only send dry wow
change your condition yeah
completely yes
very easy to manage it yeah
you check it out this design yeah
and then you can do it yeah yeah
I think I can yeah
thank you for teaching me
you are a master yeah
I'm so glad no
and today is special day do you have a reference to your outfit
oh yes
I do ah
it's the same outfit yes
this is the outfit amazing nice
wow it's Princess that I hope so
I saw the your dress so I today your dress is very elegant right
so I might recommend you is in sophisticated Moody
elegant Moody I like the elegant one
ah elegant
it's here yes okay
pop it to choice thank you so much
please give it to me oh
I'm so excited today is very exciting
today it is very exciting
don't worry I trust
today's glamorous gorgeous style
so did you born in Philippines
my parents were born in the Philippines
I was born here
I used to live in Philippines really
yeah three years or where Baguio
Baguio oh
my gosh you know Baguio
ah yes
um my mom is from Bulacan and my dad is from Batangas
so we've been around alright
Baguio is so cool place so cool
can you speak any Tamil I can
I'm fluent oh
can you actually say yes
I know I can remember many things
but I can say like magandang umaga
magandang umaga ah
ha magkano dito
ah ha
magkano dito okay
that's a good one that's a good one
in the end I don't know what gusto mo patay
hahaha
no
Hindi hahaha Jenny is a very funny sister
I I can sing the traditional song
oh which payang mageliyo
oh wala SA silanganan Ang alam ng puso SA itim moy
buhay you're better than me
that's exactly right you're better than me
I don't know the song if my mom heard you
this song is a traditional song
oh traditional right
traditional yes
Sophia
It's five minutes before Sophia arrives. Oh, this is Sophia. Yes, Sophia. Sophia.
I think you'll come, yeah
Oh, I don't think Sophia can't come.
Well, Sophia suddenly said she couldn’t come, but oh really, really.
oh you're a customer I'm a customer
Ah
Yes, then how about changing it to mother?
How about changing it to motherly point makeup?
such a good idea
because
my mom
was getting this makeover
inside of me or with me because she's been through so much
okay yeah you're so like a bond to each other
you know I was sad when I realized that there was only a slot for me
and that I'd already taken it
because I'm already here on the last day
there was nothing after me and there was nothing before um
so she said you know it's okay
I just want to be there with you you know
I just want to see your joy and experience your joy
그럼 제가 말할까요 어 한번 놓쳐 보는 것도 괜찮을 거 같아요
근데 이거를 제가 말했다가 싫다고 그러시면 어떡하지 그럼 못 하는 거지
뭐 아
excuse me
actually we uh
our second guest is no coming here because of her private issue
you you want to make up or hair and makeup
with with her yeah me yeah oh my
oh my God what's the secret what's the secret
oh my God oh my God oh oh
OK yeah my daughter said OK so yeah haha yes yes OK
then I'll be ready for the makeup so I will call you OK oh OK
oh wow thank you oh my God thank you oh my God
oh my gosh that would be a miracle for me oh my gosh oh you're so nice
you guys did so good for me already I said I think I look okay
for the thing and then you look great but they're gonna do amazing
yeah yeah like you can just play with it
you're so good guys cause I'm already like I'm already old
it's like it's okay
but you guys but you guys treat yourself actually treat yourself
oh she is
oh my gosh this is really it's not even my birthday
I was willing to give it to them
thank you for yes oh
thank you my gosh
I'm so honored oh my gosh
if you want to keep your stuff
we're here OK
alright thank you
thank you so much guys oh my gosh
this is turning out to be a very surprising day 그
소피아가 소피아가 에 못 오신다 못 오신다 해서 어머니를
지금 논이 중이요 열두시 해야겠다
이 분도 시작해야겠다 actually
my second guest today will not come here because of her
private issue so
uh I give it to you mom I asked her I asked her makeover but she she
she answered yes she wants to yeah is it OK
why ah
I can play again
why
no I'm just so happy I'm just so happy yes your mom killed Perla
oh my God
I hope it to know is and you're okay with mum it's very alright
many say in the world many people say move to the
uh USA because of they want to successful life
right then you all say go
you're a successful wife whoa you're amazing
I know that her and my dad worked really hard to
make sure I grew up good here
and the reason I can do things like this is because of her so
you're a very successful wife
who isn't give it to your mom
yeah I
I know it yes
everything is for them ha
ha ha
I because of
I have one daughter one child
oh 나도 울 뻔했어 나도 울 뻔했어
because you cry we three cry oh my god we were like oh oh haha yeah
okay thank you so much
yeah thank you for for doing that for her I appreciate that
I can't take it I want to tell my
mother I want to tell my
mother
다행 헤어하고 있어서 다행이다 다행이다 아유 진짜 다행이다 아유
I will do her makeup
best okay thank you yeah thank you so much trust me
I trust you completely 선물이죠 선물 keep it too
kind people you can always trust
그 마스크 팩 하고 저기 안에서는 패드 할게요
excuse me ma'am
let's do a skincare first oh my gosh right here yeah right here
I mean just mask bag oh oh my gosh I feel like
this is even more than what I had for my wedding or anything
it's like oh my gosh
this is even more because what I had for my wedding and I'm so excited
to know did you done your makeup today or sunscreen I did
yeah this ladies help me a lot
because I have no clue what I'm doing for myself
okay can you please come this way oh yes thank you yes
thank you ladies
hello
mom yes babe hi I know that breathing
oh my gosh
you too Mommy I know I'm so honored Victoria
I I got very choked up oh my God
oh no you're gonna make us all cry again mom
love you mama oh
that's very sweet you're a family
this is my bag today close eyes please
oh you got a face mask
hahaha good good
she's learning
I know I was telling them they just taught me this last night
you know what I used to live in Philippines
oh really
yeah Baguio
oh Baguio
I was just there last um February mom
he can sing I can sing he can sing a song oh wow
Baguio change a lot though really already yes
oh wow yeah
you can relax alright
thank you
yeah Victoria's actually the one who fixed my hair this morning
oh no don't reveal that
that one yes
cause I wanted to be like the best version of myself for her today
and I do not know how to fix myself with all the makeup and the hair
so she helps me a lot
but it was beautiful oh
thank you thank you
it's okay though you should wash it away hahaha yeah
I'm sorry it's okay
it's good it's good
how's the water temperature
it's good it's good thank you
we have similar hair now oh
we do
maybe that's why I chose it subconscious in my in the back of my brain
oh
you're like this princess haha
that's so sweet
혹시 옷 입고 마무리 할까 봐요
change the your rooms and follow me
yes it's okay yes yes thank you yes okay touch your hair okay
this is your makeover oh thank you 드레스 입고 머리 마무리할게요 네
can I see the reference again yes
do you like K pop style makeup
I do yeah I do I do K pop makeup I do yeah for
K pop Idol oh my gosh yes so that's yeah my job that's amazing oh
you're welcome uh you want the glitter on the eyelid line yes uh huh
first uh can I shape your eyebrow a little bit yeah
is it okay yes it's okay uh it's gonna be the little bit
change the shape okay okay okay cool thank you so much
don't cry no crying
this is it this is the end of it yeah I heard all about it
no more crying no more crying yeah it's gonna be
a good day it's gonna be a great day yeah so don't cry
OK no crying yeah just smile yes
okay I don't um have like a straight the shape
I shape it uh huh the end the eyebrow uh huh
how's your job uh
stressful but worth it oh stressful oh
that sounds so sad it's okay though um when you see somebody
do good after you took care of them it makes everything worth it
mm hmm what is the reason you get the job
um so my mom actually has a lot of health problems
like her whole body can be very painful
like electricity like shooting
oh yeah
yeah yeah
um and she
her muscles get weak her eyes even are a little more uneven together
yeah she has one eye that droops a little more than the other yeah
so yeah so that's
that's something she that's part of the reason
it's been so hard to have her get makeup done
and to
for her to feel pretty and because it's hard to do a lot until now
she has
it's better now she has good doctors and they're working with her
you told me they're getting better now yeah
so yeah yeah
I'm happy thank you
yeah oh
thank you I just wanted to take care of people and learn what's
what's happening with the body so that I can give back to other people
the way my mom came back to me
so good so kind yeah
it's so impressive yeah
it's gonna be good day good day yeah
oh it's like a mess for me
wow it's totally different
it looks like a Korean just Korean shape
mirror oh
my mirror time
oh wow
it looks so different yes
clear wow
that's my face without the heavy eyebrows oh my God
wow thank you
so pretty thank you so much okay
you did a great job mm hmm
thank you so much should we move to makeup room
oh cool
makeup time makeup time
thank you thank you makeup time
welcome to my room oh wow
please sit down here gosh
thank you in advance
thank you for whatever miracle you're gonna do for me
you deserve it oh
I heard your daughter is doctor
so yes
yeah she graduated Magna cum laude from her school yeah
yeah she got the highest um
award when she graduated med school for neurology right
when I decided to start makeup artist
my mom really worried about me because yeah
it is really a hard way to yeah
it's a mother thing it's a mother thing
you cannot turn it off like a same way with them
I could see she's but it's still
there's one thing she would say and then I'll be like worried again ah
yes yes yes
it's a mother thing yeah
I agree until you have your own kid
I guess you would not understand it fully
mm hmm
자꾸 엄마 생각나요 왜냐면 엄마랑 되게 비슷해요 소녀 같은 그런 상해
좀 있으셔서 딱 엄마 해 드리는 마음을 해 드렸던 거 같아요 어
the last time you make up when you married
uh the the um professional one yes
yes I do not like to do makeup
I don't like to do nail polish I want everything simple mm hmm
and then I always have like a um
difficulty with my eyeshadow because I have like a hooded
like it's not equal
because I had like a condition that caused that
so okay
but let's do that close eyes please thank you
그니까 사실 그 눈이 짝짝일 때는 레시로 맞춰야 되는 게 답인 거
같아요 눈이 짝짝인데 더 쉐도우를 더 많이
더 빠르고 라이너를 더 두껍게 그리기만 하면은 너무 투디로서 차이가
It's a lot
So, rather, a recipe that can always produce that three-dimensional effect.
By putting it together, it looks very symmetrical to the eye.
It seems to be working. That's why Lesi's
I paid a little more attention. I will look more the same yeah
yeah I love this side I love this style more
this look more natural
Feeling that your eyes are relatively smaller
For that part, I will raise the eyelash a little higher and attach it.
I don't know about you but
oh my God I don't know about you but I feel good
looks so amazing yes so pretty
gosh you are amazing Leo yes I'm so happy
you can transform my face to this Leo you're
you're a wizard haha thank you
he's a miracle worker
yeah look look how I look I I never think I would look like this
miracle worker
I'm gonna use the medium color first this is copper brown
use the point color
this yellow
If you look at the clothes and the hair, you want it.
You did your hair correctly.
That's right, you don't like cute things.
I want to do it like this. Ah, it looks a little like a pear. Uh, the clothes also look like a pear.
this yellow just a little bit
oh that's good on you thanks
you want a glitter and a leaf right yeah
a little champagne color the middle size
hmm
great
wow
I look so pretty yeah
it looks so totally changed
yes mm hmm
Hello, the color of your outfit matches. Yes.
Yeah, now I'm going to add some glitter here, so I'm going to put it all on now.
After the eyes are done, the decoration is the last thing we do.
The food is the same too. Ah, that's right. After everything is done, now
Put a cupping on top of it like putting a cupping on it.
Exactly haha you understand totally of course
Okay, how did you understand?
wow
oh it's good
oh my gosh look at you oh my gosh
you look like an actress oh thank you oh my gosh
it's so beautiful oh my God
ha now it's coming out
so are you guys ready are we ready am I ready
I mean as ready as I am as ready as I am okay
just cover your eyes whatever
oh she's gonna walk out yes big reaction okay
I'm scared I'm blind and afraid hahaha
It comes out
uh my name is Victoria Castillo
I am 28 years old and I'm a second year neurology resident
here in the city my mom outside actually she has um
a neurological condition that we don't fully understand
yet and then I became a brain doctor because
I want to help people like her the doctors that took care of her
part of me wishes that she was getting this makeover
instead of me or with me because she's been through so much really
I was just saying she's my best friend
I give it to you Ma I asked her I asked her makeover but
I can say love you mama oh very sweet your family
wow
open it open it oh my God
oh
my God
I'm gonna sing it
그냥 보면 느껴졌어 되게 포지티브한
에너지 긍정적인 에너지가 확 느껴져 가지고
this yellow a little bit a little champagne color the middle side
아 이렇게 하면 저는 이제 글리터를 요렇게 얹어서 여기까지 이어지게 하고
looks like a fairy oh so pretty
I think is the nose part is huge important because the
nose is the center of the face so
not connect yeah separate because it's trend yeah so
oh it's good
oh my because of you wow
ash brown ash beige you have a dark hair with the yellow dress
oh it should be easy
oh my God so pretty
oh my
God this is so pretty oh my God
that's perfect match with this makeup
and and the dress uh huh as well she does her magic to everyone
hello hello
we're here again where are you
I didn't even know I have those hahaha
oh my gosh you look just like a Jasmine yeah just literally
oh my gosh I loved my makeover
a part of me kind of always wanted to be a sort of Disney princess
I felt like I got to have my my transformation
moment you know the end of the movie
the villain is vanquished you spin
around and then you're in a pretty dress and your hair is all done
and your makeup's great that's
that's how I feel so to be able to see a dream come true on my face
wow what a treat really
open your eyes oh
my God
oh
wait I'm actually done
wow oh
the makeup goes crazy
how to care
Tom Tom
yeah
oh my God
I was supposed to keep this one here
우와 진짜 공주님
같애 thank you so much thank you it's pony who did my makeup
it looks so good you're so pretty I feel so pretty
I keep getting lost in her eyes like it's insane thank you thank you
do you have a cell phone that I can take a picture of you for you
I don't really feel like I should stand next to you
stand here where is Tita here where is Tita yeah
아
ㅎㅎ 아 친구들 너무 웃긴다 아 진짜 ㅎㅎ
thank you so much thank you so much thank you
are you guys ready for your mom
oh my God you're sitting here in the middle
how to care I don't know
oh my God oh my God
yeah ah
I'm nervous oh my gosh I'm glad she got that reception
are you ready to go out so my turn yes
wow look at this
yes oh my gosh
you look amazing
I'm tense I can't cry if you do it's OK
open eyes open eyes open eyes open eyes
my name is Marybeth Castillo
I am 56 years old well
I'm excited to be a part of my daughter's makeover reveal
you don't mind you you want to make up or hair and makeup with
with her yeah
oh oh oh
oh
OK
oh my God oh my God
thank you in advance for whatever miracle you gonna do for me
that is really such a wonderful addition to today's experience
thinking that I was just part of a reveal
and now I'm actually in the reveal
딱 엄마 해 드리는 마음을 해 드렸던 거 같아요
blown away I was expecting something but
you actually delivered even much more than what I was expecting
today your hair is up to style
today your ring night is it
uh huh is it short uh huh is in
daytime is in put down is it little bit happy
is Korean beauty is important thing is detail
oh I really am very very much convinced
that I could look like this
especially at this age and year and everything like that
as I said it's a gift of a lifetime
thank you
oh
wow
can I hug you oh my you're so pretty oh my God you are so beautiful
honey you are so beautiful
you look so good I'm not gonna cry I'm not gonna cry you are so lovely
inside and out you are so beautiful
I love you so much I love you so much you are the closest
I think the most important thing about how she looked
when she came to me and I touched on this a little earlier
is she just looked so happy
for her to have fun like that
and to not be thinking so hard
and just to be so proud of the way that she looks
that's that's a joy that I'm gonna keep in my heart forever
oh my you're so pretty
oh my God you are so beautiful honey you are so beautiful
you look so good I'm not gonna cry
I'm not gonna cry you are so lovely
and letting us be together for it
it's so priceless we would never forget it thank you so much
I'm so hot
I'm so pretty thank you
thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank
you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
아 잠깐 ㅎㅎ 왜 울어요 늙었어요 파워 에프가
여기 있네 나 티야 ㅎㅎ
thank you you look
amazing thank you so much and thank you for all you did for my mom
oh
she looks so pretty Victoria Victoria can you stand
right there I'm gonna take a picture of just you while we're waiting
for the elevator I have some on my phone oh you do
yeah but it's for my phone ha ha
my princess
always going to be my Disney princess
thank you thank you so much ma'am
yes thank you
thank you thank you
Goodbye Goodbye Goodbye Goodbye
hello
wow that is such an experience
that is so wonderful
oh oh hi hi
oh oh hi
good to see you good to see you
welcome welcome
hi hi
hi nice to how are you oh Lana Lana nice to meet you
I'm Lana we're a very hot influencer yeah
um can I get a tea yeah what type extra hot
that's why you're so beautiful oh my god hello welcome
yeah hello hahaha this is actually a concern because the features are so pretty
The answer that suits that is like a doll, oh my god, why are you so pretty?
It's a face that can wear so many different types of makeup.
I'm so excited
too
It's pretty. Oh my god wow hi Sara and Lia Sara Lia welcome
hi how are you
I'm Sarah I'm Sarah
nice to meet you nice to meet you
yeah like a trick for your husband yeah
see if they can tell us something yeah
This, this, this, this, this, this is really fun.
Ah, it's already fun. Ah, it's already delicious. It's really the same. It's coming out. Open.
That's that
Celia, that thing really looks the same.